export default {
    name: "Tmp Quiz",
    roundsCount: 3,
    rounds: [
        {
            name: "Round 1",
            questionsCount: 3,
            questions: [
                {
                    id: "01|01",
                    question: "ABC?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "A",
                            text: "aaa"
                        },{
                            letter: "B",
                            text: "bbb"
                        },{
                            letter: "C",
                            text: "ccc"
                        },{
                            letter: "D",
                            text: "ddd"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "B"
                },{
                    id: "01|02",
                    question: "MNO?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "M",
                            text: "mmm"
                        },{
                            letter: "N",
                            text: "nnn"
                        },{
                            letter: "O",
                            text: "ooo"
                        },{
                            letter: "P",
                            text: "ppp"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "N"
                },{
                    id: "01|03",
                    question: "XYZ?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "W",
                            text: "www"
                        },{
                            letter: "X",
                            text: "xxx"
                        },{
                            letter: "Y",
                            text: "yyy"
                        },{
                            letter: "Z",
                            text: "zzz"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "X"
                }
            ]
        },{
            name: "Round 2",
            questionsCount: 4,
            questions: [
                {
                    id: "02|01",
                    question: "ABCD?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "A",
                            text: "aaa"
                        },{
                            letter: "B",
                            text: "bbb"
                        },{
                            letter: "C",
                            text: "ccc"
                        },{
                            letter: "D",
                            text: "ddd"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "A"
                },{
                    id: "02|02",
                    question: "MNOP?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "M",
                            text: "mmm"
                        },{
                            letter: "N",
                            text: "nnn"
                        },{
                            letter: "O",
                            text: "ooo"
                        },{
                            letter: "P",
                            text: "ppp"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "P"
                },{
                    id: "02|03",
                    question: "RSTU?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "R",
                            text: "rrr"
                        },{
                            letter: "S",
                            text: "sss"
                        },{
                            letter: "T",
                            text: "ttt"
                        },{
                            letter: "U",
                            text: "uuu"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "S"
                },{
                    id: "02|04",
                    question: "WXYZ?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "W",
                            text: "www"
                        },{
                            letter: "X",
                            text: "xxx"
                        },{
                            letter: "Y",
                            text: "yyy"
                        },{
                            letter: "Z",
                            text: "zzz"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "W"
                }
            ]
        },{
            name: "Round 3",
            questionsCount: 3,
            questions: [
                {
                    id: "03|01",
                    question: "ABCD!?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "A",
                            text: "aaa"
                        },{
                            letter: "B",
                            text: "bbb"
                        },{
                            letter: "C",
                            text: "ccc"
                        },{
                            letter: "D",
                            text: "ddd"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "D"
                },{
                    id: "03|02",
                    question: "MNOP!?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "M",
                            text: "mmm"
                        },{
                            letter: "N",
                            text: "nnn"
                        },{
                            letter: "O",
                            text: "ooo"
                        },{
                            letter: "P",
                            text: "ppp"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "O"
                },{
                    id: "03|03",
                    question: "WXYZ!?",
                    answers: [
                        {
                            letter: "W",
                            text: "www"
                        },{
                            letter: "X",
                            text: "xxx"
                        },{
                            letter: "Y",
                            text: "yyy"
                        },{
                            letter: "Z",
                            text: "zzz"
                        },
                    ],
                    correct: "X"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}